Hi everyone, I hope you all are doing fine.
So I have realised one thing that ever since I
shifted to Gurgaon, I have
stopped going to the free markets of Delhi
because it is so far away.  Plus it takes
2 hours to go and 2 hours to return.
But today I have got myself ready and am
going to the district for shopping.  Or
Let's Go.  Finally, after 2 hours of hard work,
we reached the district.  And this is the
inner market area of ​​the district where
I was shopping.  Honestly speaking, the
collection of every shop on the inside side was almost the
same.  I was looking at prostitutes etc. here.
And this was the shop where I
found this really nice skirt.  So
I said
we are not able to understand which one this
is for and one is this, there are so many options here.
And I will go shopping I met you guys.   I am
telling the truth.  I am enjoying meeting you.   Just do it
100%.   I will have to
work in Bhaiya's shop for three days
[laughs].  I have always
loved buying jewellery from Janpad.
This time I have explored the Tibetan market.
And I
found some really cool things.  I didn't like the Lama Art House
collection that much.  After this
I went to the West Side where the whole of Delhi had
gathered.  There was so much crowd.
I did not understand anything.  Legit,
I was out within 1 minute.  And I chose the
worst time in Delhi to travel to Delhi Gurgaon.
That is 7:30 in the evening.
Brother, it took me almost 3 hours.  There was so much
traffic, so much traffic.  The entire Google
Map was showing red.  Tired and tired
[music] I reached home at 10:30.   I will
show you the hall tomorrow.  Till Then Bye
Bye Take